# **ZORAN GJUROSKI**

Gjuro Salaj 10b, Struga, Macedonia 6330 ♦ +389 77 834 087 ♦ zoran.gjuroski@gmail.com

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Highly motivated, professional full stack software engineer with more than three years of experience in analysis, development, testing and implementation of various solutions. Proficient in agile software development and scrum methodologies. Eager to learn new technologies and new things every day. A big Data Science and Machine Learning enthusiast.

https://zorangj.github.io/ ♦ https://github.com/zorangj ♦ https://www.linkedin.com/in/zorangjuroski

#### **S**KILLS

- Fluent in C#, SQL, JavaScript
- ASP.NET (MVC), ASP.NET Core, Web API
- HTML5, CSS3, AJAX, Bootstrap, XML, JSON
- React, Angular, Redux, Vue.js, jQuery
- LINQ, LINQPad
- Microsoft Visual Studio, Microsoft SQL Server, IntelliJ
- NUnit, xUnit, Moq, Robot Framework
- Agile, SCRUM, TFS, Git, SVN
- Entity framework, Dapper
- WPF
- Team leadership skills
- Mentoring and code reviews

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Software Engineer**, 09/2016 to Current **Allocate Software** – Skopje, Macedonia

Working as a Software Engineer and Scrum Master - making sure that Scrum's best practices are followed on a daily level. Developed several new modules on the existing company's products for rostering hospital staff. Developed software architecture and initial codebase for a new product – activities management solution.

# **Software Engineer / Contractor**, 05/2017 to 10/2017

Metiq – Skopje, Macedonia

Worked on a finance solution for factoring. Work included: updating the UI of an existing app, implementing security, reports modules and a module for fees calculation.

# **Software Engineer,** 07/2015 to 09/2016

Re-Aktiv – Skopje, Macedonia

Designed and developed few components of the complex platform that represents the company's main product. Responsible for building and integrating several components and their deployment. Integrating new team members in the team and in the whole development process.

## **Software Engineer**, 02/2014 to 06/2016

**Freelance** – Skopje, Macedonia

Built several applications for customers which were contracted independently and on Upwork, including complex e-commerce web applications, financial desktop applications and Web APIs.

#### **Junior Software Engineer**, 07/2014 to 06/2015

Re-Aktiv – Skopje, Macedonia

Building solutions that solve complex business processes in state institutions (Investment Funds, Securities Exchange Commission).

**Intern**, 06/2013 to 09/2013

**Netcetera** – Skopje, Macedonia

Participated in implementing an application for the company's internal office administration processes while learning the whole web development foundation.

**EDUCATION** 

Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering, 2014

#### Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering - Skopje

- Algorithms, Data structures, OOP, Databases, Web technologies, Intelligent systems, Design Patterns

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Machine Learning [Coursera]
- CCNA Exploration: Routing Protocols and Concepts / CCNA2 [Cisco]
- CCNA Exploration: Network Fundamentals / CCNA1 [Cisco]

#### **PROJECTS**

- Planner, Allocate Software Web application for managing hospital staff activities. [ASP.NET Core, React, Redux, xUnit]
- Factoring, Metig Finance application for factoring (cash advance). [ASP.NET Core, EF Core, Angular 4, Azure1
- EmployeeOnlineMobile, Allocate Software Mobile application used by the hospital staff to track their work schedule. [Apache Cordova, Ionic, AngularJS]
- HealthRoster, Allocate Software Complex platform for creating work schedule for staff in hospitals, managing attendance, payment and also prediction of more suitable schedules for the future. [C#, LINQ, NUnit]
- TheTowawayZone, Freelance Web application for towing companies to manage the impounded vehicles. [C#, KnockoutJS, Entity Framework, SignalR]
- CoreRegistryPlatform, Re:Aktiv Generic framework for registers and business processes. Contains multiple web applications, services, plugins, document management system, messaging. [C#, SQL, Dapper, WCF]
- DenDiet, Freelance online nutrition counseling and creating custom weight loss plan/menus for customers. [C#, ASP.NET MVC, EntityFramework, SignalR, KnockoutJS]
- SaraFashion, Freelance E-commerce web application for creating orders with products. [C#, ASP.NET MVC, SQL, JavaScript]
- AtomeM, Freelance E-commerce application for online shopping. [C#, ASP.NET MVC, SQL, JavaScript]
- eSF, Re:Aktiv Configurable web platform which offers different kind of services, payment, integration. [C#, ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework]
- SRIS, Re:Aktiv Web application that supports and supervises the processes of supervision of the capital market in Macedonia. [C#, ASP.NET MVC, WCF, SQL]
- e-Archive, Freelance Generic desktop application for archiving documents which integrates with other financial systems. [C#, WPF]
- CokeSAM, Freelance Web API for sharing coupons and messages for McDonald's meals. [C#, WEB API, Entity
- MarkoskiK73, Freelance Website for an engineering company and its work. [HTML, CSS]
- Admin Office, Netcetera Java web application for office administration. [Java, NHibernate, AngularJS1
- Graduate work Creating a knowledge base using NLP and Semantic Web. [C#, ASP.NET MVC]

#### **LANGUAGES**

## Native language: Macedonian

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	
English	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
French	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1

Levels: A1/2: Basic user - B1/2: Independent user - C1/2 Proficient user Common European Framework of Reference for Languages